trails-end.com 2008-12-20

# Trail’s End Privacy Statement

                           Trail’s End Privacy Statement
General
              This privacy statement covers the site www.trails-end.com. Because we want to
              demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we have agreed to disclose
              our information practices.
                          1. What personally identifiable information Trail’s End collects.
                          2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect
                             through the Web site.
                          3. What organization collects the information.
                          4. How Trail’s End uses the information.
                          5. With whom Trail’s End may share user information.
                          6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and
                             distribution of the information.
                          7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss,
                             misuse or alteration of information under Trail’s End control.
                          8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
      If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should
      contact the Trail’s End Webmaster by email at webmaster@trails-end.com.
              By using our Web site, users agree to be bound by the terms of the policy.
              Trail’s End collects information from our users at several different points on
              www.trails-end.com, and this information is used only as described in this policy.
              The Boy Scouts of America councils (“councils”) are affiliated partners in the
              Trail’s End program, and have access to use this information as described below.
Information Collection
      Registration
              In order to use some of the features of this web site, a user must first complete
              the registration process by providing personally identifiable information, such as
              name, address, email or phone number. Users may also be asked to provide
              certain aggregate information in registration that is anonymous (such as an IP
              address, income level or gender). User names and passwords are also included
              in the information that may be requested during registration.
      Ordering
              We request further information from the user on our order form. A user must
              provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and
              additional financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).
              This sensitive information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s
              orders. The financial information is not shared with any organization other than
              Trail’s End. Financial information is never shared with the councils. If we have
              trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

Information Use
           General Disclosure
                   These are the limited instances in which we will share users’ personal
                   information:
                   Intermediaries. We may disclose users’ personal information to third party
                   intermediaries, such as a third party shipping company to ship orders, and a
                   credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These
                   companies are not allowed to retain, share, store or use personally identifiable
                   information for any purposes other than those contracted by Trail’s End or the
                   councils.
                   Service Providers. We partner with other third parties to provide specific
                   services. For example, in 2003, the prize program for scouts will require an
                   online credited purchase from a third party. When the user signs up for these
                   particular services, we may share names or other contact information that is
                   necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are
                   not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of
                   providing these services.
                   Business Partners. The system on this Web site exists to support the councils in
                   its popcorn sales program. Information provided to Trail’s End will be made
                   available to the councils as needed to run their programs. This includes
                   personally identifiable information, addresses, phone numbers, email, and
                   previous orders. The councils may provide this information to their districts and
                   units for the purposes of annual selling or any other purpose. However, the
                   information provided to the councils does not include any personal financial or
                   credit card information.
           Profile
                   We store information that we collect through database files to create a profile of
                   our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that
                   details their viewing permissions. Consequently, collected information is tied to
                   the users personally identifiable information. This profile is used to tailor a user’s
                   visit to our web site, and to direct pertinent content. The profile information may
                   be made available to the councils and other third party service providers.
           Surveys and Contests
                   From time-to-time our site may request information from users related to surveys
                   or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary
                   and the user, therefore, has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.
                   The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name
                   and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).
                   Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.
                   Anonymous Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or
                   improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users’ personally identifiable
                   information is not shared with third parties, other than the councils, unless we
                   give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct
                   these surveys or contests, they may not use users’ personally identifiable
                   information for any secondary purposes.
INIMAN2 650228v2                                    -2-                                 http://www.trails-end.com

           Legal Use
                  Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose
                  personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief
                  that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court
                  order or legal process served on our Web site.
           Communications from the Site or Affiliates
                  We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username
                  belong to a valid email address. We and/or our affiliates may send out technical
                  and service-related announcements. For instance, if our service is temporarily
                  suspended for maintenance, we might send users an email. We and/or our
                  affiliates communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested
                  services and regarding account issues. In addition, the councils or related
                  affiliates may send out promotional emails from time to time.
           Aggregate Information
                  We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and
                  affiliates. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
Cookies
                  A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information
                  about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the
                  session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.
                  A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an
                  extended period of time. The user can remove persistent cookies by following the
                  help file instructions included with their browser.
Log Files
                  We use log files including internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet
                  service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and
                  number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in
                  the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP
                  addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links
                  This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Trail’s End and
                  its affiliates are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We
                  encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the
                  privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally
                  identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information
                  collected by this Web site.
Children’s Privacy
                  We encourage parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their
                  children's online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children’s Online Privacy
                  Protection Act and will not knowingly register or otherwise collect personally
                  identifiable information from any child.
INIMAN2 650228v2                                     -3-                                  http://www.trails-end.com

Security
                  This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When
                  users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected
                  both online and off-line.
                  When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such
                  as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is
                  encrypted and is protected with the industry standard encryption software - SSL.
                  While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of
                  Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer
                  becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.
                  While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we take
                  additional precautions to protect user-information off-line. Only employees who
                  need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a billing clerk or a
                  customer service representative) are granted access to financial information. All
                  Trail’s End associates are required to sign an Electronic Mail and Internet policy.
                  This document outlines acceptable use and security policies for all Trail’s End
                  computer systems including the Trail’s End Web site.
                  Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure
                  environment, and the financial information is stored in a separate database with
                  limited system access in a locked facility.
Correcting and Deleting Personal Information
                  If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone,
                  email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a
                  way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable
                  information. This can usually be done at the self-edit page or by contacting your
                  council.
Notification of Changes
                  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this
                  privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our users are
                  always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what
                  circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with
                  the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
                  If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a
                  manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via
                  email. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that
                  do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a
                  prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases
                  when we post a notice we will also email users notifying them of the changes in
                  our privacy practices.
           Contact Information
                  If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please
                  contact us at:
                           help@trails-end.com
                           http://www.trails-end.com
INIMAN2 650228v2                                    -4-                               http://www.trails-end.com
